#### Contact

adthai.me@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/andy-t-b567a2235 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

SQL

C (Programming Language) Java

Certifications
HTML Essential Training

# Andy Thai

CS @ UW Seattle, Minoring in Business | Paul Allen Center of Computer Science and Engineering

Seattle, Washington, United States

## Summary

A first-generation upcoming fourth-year student pursuing a degree in Computer Science and minoring in Business at the University of Washington Seattle, set to graduate in the Spring of 2024. Sufficient knowledge of Java, Python, C, SQL, and SQL++. A collaborative and detail-oriented individual, who is searching for internships and research labs related to these skills.

Always optimistic and enthusiastic about opportunities, ready to take on any challenges and learn from them. Communicative while collaborating with peers and mentors alike to tackle class projects as a team.

## Projects:

CSE 484 Vulnerability Lab (Spring 2023): As a team, we determined various bugs in the application that are used by an exploit, proposing fixes for the application as patches. Root cause analyses (RCA) are written as reflections of our patchwork as a team.

# Experience

Kakigori Dessert Cafe Food Server September 2022 - Present (1 year 1 month) Seattle, Washington, United States

- Bringing out orders and refilling ingredients within a fast-paced environment, while making high
- quality desserts and drinks as a team.
- Counting transactions to make certain every amount is correctly counted each day.
- Maintaining a clean space for workers and customers to ensure satisfaction.

Ross Stores, Inc. Sales Associate

### June 2020 - May 2022 (2 years)

Seattle, Washington, United States

- Providing the best possible customer service within a fast-paced environment.
- Counting transactions to ensure no fraudulent issues.
- Stocking products while keeping track of the flow of products in and out of the store.
- Providing a safe space for everyone as a team.
- Assisting customers when needed, including the peak hours.

#### Team Read

Tutor

October 2016 - August 2017 (11 months)

Seattle, Washington, United States

Tutoring students grades 1-5 to enhance students' reading comprehension skills and vocabulary.

# Education

University of Washington
Bachelor's degree, Computer Science (2020 - 2024)

Franklin High School

· (2016 - 2020)